we're using an app called faith a lot of
inanç denilen bir uygulamayı çok kullanıyoruz
live Sasha get over here a little bit
Sasha biraz buraya gelsin
because you're getting cut off there
çünkü orada kesiyorsun
we've got Face Swap live here we've got
Yüz Swap'ımızı burada yaşıyoruz.
the ability to swap faces or swap faces
yüzleri değiştirebilir veya yüzleri değiştirebilir
in a photo Wow now face swap live is a
bir fotoğrafta Wow şimdi yüz takas canlı bir
bail available as a free version on
kefalet ücretsiz bir sürüm olarak kullanılabilir
either iOS or Android here we're on
Burada iOS veya Android var
Android on my phone and when i click on
Android telefonumda ve tıkladığımda
it to face swap you'll see that i start
takasla yüzleşmeye başladığımı göreceksin
to see a border around my face do you
yüzümün etrafında bir sınır görmek için
guys see that now it tells me okay move
çocuklar şimdi bana iyi hareket ettiğini söylüyor
two faces into the scene Sasha you want
İstediğiniz sahneye iki yüzü Sasha
to get in on this action oh yeah okay Oh
bu aksiyona girmek için oh evet tamam
what's my fav they swap face swap oh you
yüzüm takas yapmam onlar ne?
had my face protection oh no oh did I
yüzümü korumam vardı oh hayır
get it no phased out okay hold it back
onu aşamalı yok tamam bekle geri
hold it back there we go we are lovely
Onu arkaya tut, gidelim, çok güzeliz
okay that's beautiful ah there it is
tamam bu güzel ah var
okay turn a tenon get in on this action
tamam bu eyleme giriş yap
this is faithful I'd point hahaha but
bu sadık hahaha ama
actually we're gonna miss amazing having
aslında sahip olduğumuzu özleyeceğiz
too much fun I the show so they face la
çok eğlenceli onlar la karşı karşıya böylece gösterisi
blog in real time allows you to swap
Blog gerçek zamanlı olarak takas etmenizi sağlar
faces with your friends the kids
arkadaşlarınla ​​yüzler çocuklar
absolutely adore it you can download it
kesinlikle tapıyorum onu ​​indirebilirsiniz
for free and of course there is a
ücretsiz ve tabii ki bir
commercial version that gives you some
size biraz veren ticari versiyon
extra features that you don't normally
normalde yapmadığınız ekstra özellikler
have in the free version that is Face
Face olan ücretsiz versiyona sahip olmak
Swap live.com make sure you check it out
Live.com'u değiştirdiğinizden emin olun
it is so much fun I have identical twin
o kadar eğlenceli ki aynı ikiz var
sisters yeah that Colleen before yeah
kızkardeşler evet evet önce Colleen
riot out have you met happen no well
isyan çıkardın iyi oldu
they have done a face swap yeah and it's
bir yüz değişimi yaptılar evet
funny because there they are I look I
çünkü oradalar.
than they are identical imporant want a
onlar aynı imporant istiyorlar
swap it's still kind of creepy really
takas hala tüyler ürpertici gerçekten
yeah I really sorry pop it's like
evet gerçekten üzgünüm gibi pop
slightly uncomfortable at all times it's
her zaman biraz rahatsız edici
painless that's a goodness yeah it
acısız bir iyilik evet evet
doesn't hurt we're going to do things
incitmez şeyler yapacağız
like put like kiss rock star kind of
öpücük rock yıldızı gibi koymak
face on yeah and do the rock star think
yüzüne evet ve rock yıldızı düşün
there's a ton of stuff you can do with
yapabileceğin bir sürü şey var
that app that is so much fun even put
o kadar eğlenceli olan bu uygulama bile
yourself you can actually in
aslında kendinde olabilirsin
real time you can actually change your
gerçek zaman aslında değiştirebilirsiniz
own faith using math so watch this I
matematik kullanarak kendi inancını bu yüzden izleyin
switch to a mask oh oh my gosh the
Bir maske geçiş aman aman aman
kitten is me okay there we go that's
yavru kedi benim tamam mı ?
going to skate there's me as a kitten
kaymaya gidiyorum bir yavru kedi olarak var
that's or a puppy dog or what am I going
Bu ya da bir köpek yavrusu köpek ya da ne gidiyorum
to look like when I'm old that's awfully
çok yaşlı olduğum zamanki gibi görünmek
get so you can see how it kind of phases
Nasıl olsun , nasıl bir aşama olduğunu görebilirsiniz.
in and out but it is really really good
içeri ve dışarı ama gerçekten çok iyi
for real time and then I can just take a
gerçek zamanlı ve sonra sadece alabilirim
snapshot and boom I've got a picture ok
anlık görüntü ve boom Tamam bir fotoğrafım var
never mind through that Halloween
Cadılar Bayramını boşver
special you ready faster and yeah it
özel hazır daha hızlı ve evet
kind of does new profile picture oh gosh
türkçe yeni profil resmi oh gosh
nice you guys mustache sweet ok what is
beyler güzel tatlı millet ne güzel
it yeah that's the math teacher we can
Evet, işte bu matematik öğretmeni.
do stuff like this in real time I like
gerçek zamanlı olarak böyle şeyler yapmak hoşuma gidiyor
this one oh ok yes I look like a fat
bu bir evet tamam evet şişman gibi görünüyorum
panda manage that Oh gone are the days
panda yönetin, o günler gitti
where you have to spend a whole lot of
bir sürü yer harcamak zorunda olduğunuz yer
time in Photoshop or something like that
Photoshop'taki zaman ya da böyle bir şey
it's to achieve on taneously its rate
onun oranına merhametle ulaşmak
all the spa boom just like that it's a
tüm spa patlaması tıpkı bunun gibi
lot of fun
Çok eğlenceli
[Music]
[Müzik]